h-farm.com 2019-05-17

# Privacy Policy | H-FARM

Information concerning the use of personal details as per Legislative Decree 196/2003

Dear user, 

this policy aims at providing details of the processing, and related methods of use, of personal data referred to users/visitors of this website. Web users and visitors are recommended to read carefully this policy before sending any personal information and/or filling in any electronic form posted on this website.  
This information is given in accordance with art. 13, Legislative Decree 196/2003 (Italian Data Protection Code).   
The data controller is H-FARM S.p.A., a company with registered office in Via Sile 41, 31056, Roncade, VAT no. 03944860265 (hereinafter the "Company"). In particular, the Company aims at supporting the creation of new business models and the digital transformation and education of companies and young people (hereinafter the "Activity").

**A. Data Controller**

The http://www.h-farm.com/website (hereinafter the "Website") is managed by the Company.  
The Company may collect and process the following personal information of the user:

  * Name
  * Surname
  * Email Address
  * Address
  * Telephone number

(plus any other information provided in the resume, which is at the candidate’s discretion)

(hereinafter the "Data").

**B. Purposes of the processing**

Any personal information given or collected by connecting to the Website will be processed by the Company as data controller.

The information we collect, including personal information, are used for the following: to fulfill the user’s requests (e.g. management of requests for information); to communicate with the users for purposes related to the job application process; to provide the services and/or participation to initiatives and events available through the Website.

When the users are requested to provide personal information, e.g. when registering on the Website, the Company will inform them what personal information is necessary for the registration and what is optional. Failure to provide some items of information may make it impossible to proceed with the Activity. The provision of other information is entirely optional, but if not provided, some of the features of the services offered by the Company might be unavailable or limited.

Newsletter:  
Upon the user’s consent, the Data we collect through the newsletter subscription form (name, surname, email address) are used for sending communications and periodic updates, including invitations to events organized or managed by the Company. The provision of this Data is necessary to complete the subscription and register for the newsletter: if the user doesn’t provide the Data requested, he/she will not receive the Company’s newsletter. If a user wants to opt out of the newsletter service, he/she may do so at any time by following the instructions in each newsletter or by sending a communication to the Company.

Careers:  
The Data we collect through the http://careers.h-farm.com/ webpage are used for evaluating and contacting candidates. The provision of this Data is necessary to answer to the candidate’s request: if the user doesn’t provide the Data requested, the Company will not be able to evaluate the candidate and making hiring decisions.

**C. Data Management**

Data will be processed manually or using IT or web tools by the Company staff and collaborators and/or by external collaborators designated as Data processors. In carrying out the activities provided by these individuals, the Company gives operating instructions and rules of conduct on processing personal information in compliance with this Privacy Policy.

The complete list of Data processors may be requested by contacting H-FARM Spa, via Sile 41, 31056, Roncade (Italy) or by sending an email to info@h-farm.com.

**D. Transfer and Sharing Information**

Your Data will be processed both within the Company and with third parties to whom the Company gave detailed operating instructions to guarantee the confidentiality and security of Data.

The Data will not be disclosed for any purpose, but may be shared with third parties:

  * suppliers of services to manage the Computer Systems and the Website (e.g. hosting providers, market and analyst service providers, database management and maintenance services);
  * subjects carrying out control, audit and certification activities for the business conducted by the Company, even in its interest;
  * consultants and other suppliers of related services.

**E. User's rights in relation to personal information**  
According to section 7 of the Italian data protection code, the user has certain rights, including the right to:

(I) obtain confirmation of the existence of personal data concerning him/her;  
(II) be informed of the Data content and origin, of the purposes and methods of the processing and of the logic applied to data processing if carried out with the aid of electronic means;  
(III) request that his/her information is updated, supplemented or rectified;  
(IV) request that data processed in violation of the law be erased, anonymized or blocked, and to object to any further processing of this information for legitimate reasons;  
(V) object to the processing of personal data concerning him/her, where it is carried out for the purpose of sending advertising materials or direct selling or to conduct market or communication surveys.

In order to exercise these rights and to request information relating to the users’ data we keep, you may write to info@h-farm.com.

**F. Links to third party websites**

This Privacy Policy exclusively applies to our Website.  
While browsing, contents may be seen that link to third party websites. The Company cannot access or control the cookies or the other functions used by third parties, and the procedures of those outside websites are not regulated by our Privacy Policy. Consequently, you should contact and/or directly consult those third parties for additional information on their privacy protection procedures.

**G. Cookie  Policy**

The responsible use of cookies and web beacons (aka: action tags or pixel gifs) plays an important role in the services that the Company and its affiliates provide to clients. Our services allow our clients to better serve you, their customer. The Company and its affiliates may use cookie and web beacon technology for planning, serving, analyzing, and managing online campaigns on behalf of our clients.

We use cookies for the following purposes:

**Technical cookies:  **are defined as those used for the sole purpose of _"carrying out the transmission of a communication over an electronic communications network, or as strictly necessary for a service provider of information society service explicitly requested by the subscriber or user to provide this service"  _(cfr. art. 122, paragraph 1, of the Code).

They are not used for further purposes and are normally installed directly by the owner or web site manager. They can be divided in navigation cookies and session cookies, which guarantee the navigation and the use of the Website (allowing, for example, a purchase or  the authentication of reserved areas); analytics cookies, assimilate to technical cookies when used directly by the site administrator to gather aggregated information about the number of users and how they visit the Website itself; functionality cookies, which allow users the navigation of the web according to a set of selected criteria (for example, language, products selected for purchase) to optimize the browsing experience of the User.

**TYPE OF COOKIE** | **COOKIE NAME** | **DESCRIPTION** | **WHERE  IT IS USED** | **EXPIRATION DATE** | **SOURCE**  
---|---|---|---|---|---  
Technical: navigation/session cookies | ce_cookie | It remembers if users accept cookies | All pages | 1 year | h-farm.com  
  
For the installation of these cookies no consent is required from the users.

**Profiling cookies** : are used to create profiles related to the user and are used in order to send advertising messages in line with the preferences expressed by the same part, as part of browsing the net.

The Website does not directly collect this type of cookie.

**Third-party cookies** : These cookies allow you to create anonymous user profile based on their browsing experience on this and all other sites. In this way, you can provide targeted advertising on your interests instead of generic advertising. These cookies are not managed by our company and are under the name of _third party cookies_.

This Website uses social media plug-ins furnished by the most important social networks (e.g. facebook.com and twitter.com). When visiting the webpage the browsing data may be transferred directly to the social networks concerned, even without a user’s direct interaction. The user acknowledges and agrees that the operation of social networks' plug-ins is managed directly by the company that manages the corresponding plug-in. When the users use the plug-ins available through the Website, the User’s browser establishes a direct connection with the server of that social network, which sends the contents of the plug-in directly to the user’s browser. Any information communicated to the social network will be subject to the privacy policy and the terms and conditions of that social network.

To prevent those social network from collecting the personal information of the user, please check the relevant conditions on the social networks' websites.

**COOKIE NAME**

| 

**DOMAIN**

| 

**EXPIRATION  DATE **

| 

**DESCRIPTION**

| 

**INFORMATION LINK AND CONSENT MODULES**  
  
---|---|---|---|---  
_ga  
_gid | Google Analytics  | 2 years | Cookie used by Google Analytics for statistical purposes. | <https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=it>  
_gat_UA-4597657-4 | Session  
_dc_gtm_UA-4597657-4 | Session | Cookie used by Google Analytics to track user activity for statistical purposes.   
  
**Warning:  **Proceeding through the navigation of the website, during your first visit to the website, you have consented to the collection of cookies, as specified in this notice.

**Options for the use of cookies**

It is possible to visit the Website without cookies, although in this case some parts of the Website may not work as intended or may not work at all. Most of the browsers accept cookies automatically.

You can then change your browser settings so that cookies are deleted or not saved on your computer or mobile device without your explicit consent. The automatic registration of cookies can be avoided by selecting the "do not accept cookies" option from those proposed or you can manage your browser settings. Because each browser has slightly different features, check the "Help" menu of your browser to see how to change cookie settings correctly.

Check out the following link for managing better your browser’s cookies:
